

(鄭詠云)Yung-Yun Daphney Cheng

My name is Daphney, I have graduated from high school for one year, and I graduated from ISEP of BCIT. I had part-time work experience in high school; I learn a lot of skills of coordinate with other people and the skills of communication. I believe I am a good worker and work partner.

F in

Student British Columbia · CA

E-mail: dcheng0726@gmail.com

Tel: +1(236)889-9836

Skills

Language skills

- · Proficient in Chinese and English
- Fair Taiwanese

Microsoft

- Excel, Word, Power point...etc
- The prospectus

Work Experiences

Experience 01 · Sep, 2014 - Aug, 2017

Part-time work in the school organization

- Maintain traffic order for the high school students and workers.
- Layout of examination venue.
- Help with examinee and answer examinee's questions.
- Maintain the safety of the examination area.
- Clean up the examination room.
- Distribute the work for my partners to held the activity.

Experience 02 · Dec, 2018 - Jul, 2019

Part-time work in bauble tea place: comebuy

- Make drinks
- · Help costumer to ordered
- Cook the baubles
- Cook tea

Education

The Affiliated Zhongli Senior High School of National Central University · Sep, 2014 - Jun, 2017

Campaign group leader in the school organization for safety patrol

• Held many kinds of activities

British Columbia Institute of Technology · Oct, 2017 - Dec, 2018

International Student Entry Program (ISEP), Physical 11, Math 12, Biology 12

British Columbia Institute of Technology · Sep, 2019 - now Computer Information Technology (CIT)

Powered by **CakeResume**